[{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 1",
    "question": "The upper limbs are composed of 04 segments, which are:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Arm, forearm, wrist and hand",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Arm, forearm, hand and fingers",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Cingulate of the upper limb, arm, forearm and hand",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Cingulate of the upper limb, arm, forearm and fingers",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 2",
    "question": "Which cingulate of the upper limb is formed by bones?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Humerus and ulna",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Humerus and clavicle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Scapula and humerus",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Scapula and clavicle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 3",
    "question": "Which bones and arms are composed respectively by bones?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Humerus, clavicle and ulna",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Humerus, radius and ulna",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Humerus, radius and scapula",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Humerus, clavicle and scapula",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 4",
    "question": "As for the location, the ulna bone is found:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "On the forearm, medially disposed",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "On the forearm, arranged laterally",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "On the arm, disposed laterally",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "On the arm, medially disposed",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 5",
    "question": "As for the location, the radio bone is:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "On the arm, disposed laterally",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "On the arm, medially disposed",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "On the forearm, arranged laterally",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "In the forearm, medially disposed",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 6",
    "question": "Which of the following structures is not located in the scapular bone?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Acromion",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Coracoid process",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Glenoid cavity",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Lateral supraepicondylar crest",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 7",
    "question": "Of the following structures, which is not located in the clavicle bone?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Deltoid tubule",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Pterium",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Groove of the subclavian muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Trapezoid line",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 8",
    "question": "The carpal bones in the proximal row, from lateral to medial, are respectively:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Scaphoid, semilunar, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Scaphoid, capitate, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trapeze, trapezoid, capitate and hamate",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Trapeze, trapezoid, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 9",
    "question": "The carpal bones of the distal row, from lateral to medial, are respectively:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Scaphoid, semilunar, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Scaphoid, capitate, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trapeze, trapezoid, capitate and hamate",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Trapeze, trapezoid, pyramidal and pisiform",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 10",
    "question": "The skeleton of the hand is composed of metacarpal bones. Among the alternatives below, which one is correct?",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "There are 05 bones, the 1st metacarpal bone being the thickest and shortest of the metacarpal bones",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "There are 10 bones, the 5th metacarpal bone being the thickest and shortest of the metacarpal bones",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "There are 5 bones, the 1st metacarpal bone being the thinnest and longest of the metacarpal bones",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "There are 10 bones, and the 5th metacarpal bone is the thinnest and longest of the metacarpal bones",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 11",
    "question": "Which of the following nerves does not participate in the innervation of the upper limbs?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Intercostobrachial nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Ulnar nerve",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Abducent nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Median nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 12",
    "question": "Which of the following veins is not part of the vascularization of the upper limbs?",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Obturator vein",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Cephalic vein",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Axillary vein",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Basilic vein",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 13",
    "question": "Of the following muscles, which is not part of the upper limbs?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Trapezius muscle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Deltoid Muscle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Subscapularis muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Sartorius Muscle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 14",
    "question": "The armpit is subdivided into 06 parts, which are:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Top, base, left side wall, right side wall, central region and thoracic portion",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Top, base, left side wall, right side wall, intimate wall and central wall",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Apex, base, anterior wall, posterior wall, medial wall and lateral wall",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Apex, base, bottom wall, top wall, side wall and medial wall",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 15",
    "question": "Which artery is a continuation of the axillary artery? ",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Subclavian artery continuation, starting at the lateral margin of the 1st rib, and ending at the lower margin of the teres major muscle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Continuation of the subclavian artery, starting at the lateral margin of the 3rd rib, and ending at the lower margin of the teres minor muscle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Continuation of the thoracoacromial artery, starting at the margin of the 1st rib, and ending at the lower margin of the teres minor muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Continuation of the thoracoacromial artery, beginning at the margin of the 3rd rib, and ending at the lower margin of the teres major muscle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 16",
    "question": "Of the following arteries, which is not a branch of the axillary artery?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Upper thoracic artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Subscapular artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Thoracoacromial artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Radial artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 17",
    "question": "Which of the following arteries is not part of the vascularization of the upper limb?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Subscapular artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Brachial artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Popliteal artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Ulnar artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 18",
    "question": "With respect to the brachial plexus, it is formed by which branches of nerves?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Formed by the union of the posterior branches of the nerves C5 to C7, and by the smaller part of the anterior branch of T2",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Formed by the union of the anterior branches of nerves C5 to C8 and most of the anterior branch of T1",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Formed by the union of the posterior branches of nerves C4 to C7, and most of the posterior branch of T1",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Formed by the union of the anterior branches of the nerves from C3 to C8, and by most of the posterior branch of T2",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 19",
    "question": "Of the nerves below, which is not part of the innervation of the upper limbs?",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Tibial nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Median nerve",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Medial pectoral nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Ulnar nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "superior",
    "title": "Question 20",
    "question": "Which of the following muscles is not part of the arm?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Biceps brachii muscle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Brachial Triceps muscle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trapezius muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Anceous Muscle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
}]